珍妮丝有个问题 你们六个人之中…
Janice has a question. Who of the six of you...
谁和你们六人之中的任何人上床过
...has slept with who of the six of you?
哇 很像下流的数学问题
Wow, it's like a dirty math problem.
很抱歉 答案是谁都没有
I'm sorry, the answer there would be none of us.
少来了 这么多年来 你们没有人喝醉做过蠢事吗
Over the years, none of you ever got drunk and stupid?
这是个全然不同的问题
Well, that's really a different question.
对不起 我只是很难相信 这么常在一起的一群人…
I can't believe a group of people who spends this much time together...
没碰过这样的糗事
...has never bumped uglies.
是有一次 摩妮卡和瑞秋聚在一起
There was that one time Monica and Rachel got together.
什么
What?
抱歉 根本没有
Excuse me, there was no time.
好吧 假装有的话
Okay, but let's say there was.
会是什么景象呢
How might that go?
好了…
Okay, okay.
再回答一个问题
Well, then answer me this:
你们有人曾经差一点吗…
Have any of you ever almost?
- 谁要多一点咖啡吗   - 外面有只狗耶
- Anybody need more coffee?     - Hey, there's a dog out there!
# 没有人告诉你活着有多累 #
# So no one told you life was gonna be this way #
# 上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘 #
# Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. #
# 寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累 #
# It's like you're always stuck in second gear #
# 日复一日 年复一年 #
# When it hasn't been your day, #
# 时运不济 活着受罪 #
# your week, your month, or even your year #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# but I'll be there for you #
# 纵有狂风暴雨 #
# When the rain starts to pour #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# I'll be there for you #
# 支持一如往昔 #
# Like I've been there before #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# I'll be there for you #
# 你我相偎相依 #
# 'Cause you're there for me too #
（三年前）
- 太不幸了  - 怎么了
- Ugh. That is so unfortunate.     - What?
帅气裸男开始变胖了
Cute Naked Guy's starting to put on weight.
我很快就回来
I'll be back in just a minute.
菲比 很抱歉 我在电话上留下口红印
I'm sorry that I left lipstick marks on the phone.
你没有啊
You didn't leave lipstick marks on the phone.
那一定是你 拜
Oh! Then it must have been you. Bye.
拜拜
Bye-bye.
- 那就是我搬出去的原因   - 既然谈到这个…
- That's why I moved out.     - Hey, while we're on that...
你什么时候才要跟我妹说 你已经不住在这里了
...when are you gonna tell my sister you don't live here anymore?
我觉得她在某种程度上 已经知道了
On some level, she already knows.
菲比 她不知道你每晚都溜出去
She doesn't know you sneak out every night...
不知道早上又溜回来
...and back every morning...
也不知道你在你外婆那里住了一个礼拜了
...and that you've been at your grandmother's for a week.
好吧 那些细节她可能不知道
Okay, well, maybe not on those levels.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
我找不到室友了 永远都找不到
I'm never gonna find a roommate. Ever.
找不到适合的人
Nobody good?
有一个家伙养雪貂
There was the guy with the ferrets.
不只一只
That's plural.
吐口水的家伙 对了 还有超爱我名字的那个人
The spitter. Oh! And the guy who enjoyed my name so much...
每次说我的名字就得来点音效
...he made a noise every time he said it.
"很高兴认识你 钱德宾 宾 "
"Nice to meet you, Chandler Bing. Bing!"
"很棒的公寓 钱德宾 宾 "
"Great apartment, Chandler Bing. Bing!"
- 明天还要见几个人   - 两个
- How many more tomorrow?     - Two.
一位看起来很闷的摄影师
This photographer who seemed really dull...
还有一个演员 我不太确定他好不好
...and this actor guy who I'm not sure about.
因为他打来 我接起来说 "我是钱德宾时"
When I answered the phone, "Chandler Bing"...
他说"哇 好短的语音留言"
...he said, "Whoa! Short message!"
罗斯…
Ross...
脚放在地上 不然以后就不欢迎你了
Foot on the floor or come over no more.
你的衣橱不见了 她却只注意到这个
Your dresser is missing, but this she notices.
- 什么   - 我得走了
- What?     - I have to go. Heh.
卡萝应该回到家了 所以…
Carol should be home by now, so...
- 你们俩个情况如何   - 好多了 其实
- How's it going with you guys?     - Better, actually.
我终于知道为什么我们最近问题这么多了
I finally figured out why we're having so much trouble.
- 真的吗   - 对 我有你们这班好朋友
- Oh, really?     - Yeah. You know how I have you guys?
她没有自己的一群好友
She doesn't have any close friends that are just hers.
但是上星期 她在健身房认识一个叫苏珊的人
But last week, she met this woman at the gym, Susan something.
她们感情变得很好 我觉得这会让情况有所改变
And they really hit it off, and I think it's gonna make a difference.
那么 艾瑞克…
So, uh, Eric...
你是哪类的摄影师
...what kind of photography do you do?
大部分是时尚
Oh, mostly fashion.
所以可能偶尔会有模特儿过来 希望你没问题
There may be models here sometimes. I hope that's cool.
没有问题
Yes, that is cool.
因为这里…模特儿…
Uh, because I have models here, you know...
从来不会来
...never.
夏天时 我在周末大部分会在我姊姊海滩的家
Ooh! During the summer, I spend most weekends at my sister's beach house...
也很欢迎你来
...which you're welcome to use.
但我得先告诉你 她是A片女星
Although I should tell you, she's a porn star.
嗯 我还得跟一个人面谈
Well, I still have one more person to meet.
但除非那个人是你姊姊…
But unless it turns out to be your sister...
不然你的机会应该很大
...ahem, I think your chances are pretty good.
好吧
All right.
卧房 厕所 客厅
Bedroom, bathroom, living room.
这是厨房 谢谢你过来 再见
This here is the kitchen, and thanks for coming by. Bye-bye.
你不想问点问题吗
Don't you, uh, wanna ask me any questions?
当然
Sure. Uh... Hmm...
有什么新鲜事
What's up?
嗯 我是演员
Well, I'm an actor.
我还蛮干净的
I'm fairly neat.
我有自己的电视
I got my own TV.
噢 别担心 我对同性恋绝对没异议
Oh, and don't worry, I'm totally okay with the gay thing.
什么同性恋
Ha, ha. What gay thing?
你知道 就是一般… 有人是同性恋
Uh, just, you know, in general. The whole people-being-gay thing.
我完全没问题
Totally cool with that.
好吧 杰瑞 谢谢你过来
Okay, Jerry. Thanks for stopping by.
- 嗨   - 嘿
- Hi.     - Hey.
天啊
Oh, my God!
嘿 小摩
Hey, Mon.
- 想听点糟透的事吗   - 我想听吗
- Wanna hear something that sucks?     - Do I ever!
- 克里斯说他们要关闭酒吧    - 不会吧
- Chris says they're closing the bar.     - No way!
他们要改成什么咖啡厅
They're turning it into a coffee place.
只卖咖啡
Just coffee?
- 那我们要去哪里聚会   - 问倒我了
- Where are we gonna hang out?     - You got me.
- 麻烦给我一罐啤酒    - 你找到室友了吗
- Can I get a beer?     - Did you pick a roommate?
- 没错   - 是那个意大利人吗
- You bet.     - Is it the Italian guy?
是啊
Hmm, yeah, right.
他好可爱
He's so cute.
是啊 我正需要这样的室友跟他走在一起
That's what I want. A roommate I can walk around with...
大家都说他是好笑的那个
...and be referred to as "the funny one."
球桌空下来了 把球排好 很快回来
Table's free. Rack them up. Back in a minute.
等着我给你好看吧
Get ready for me to whip your butt.
好 但在那之后 我们要打点撞球
Okay, but after that we're shooting some pool.
不对… 不好意思 麻烦一下
Oh, ahem, no, no, no. Excuse me? Hello? Hi.
我的朋友点了加洋葱的
My friend ordered an onion...
不是加橄榄的
...not an olive.
我点的是兰姆酒加健怡可乐
And I ordered a rum and Diet Coke...
这杯应该不是
...which I don't think this is.
- 很抱歉   - 没关系
- I am so sorry.     - That's all right.
弄杯对的饮料会有多难啊
How hard is it to get a couple drinks right, huh?
那么
Well...
我想敬杯酒…
I would like to propose a toast...
敬这位一年后会成为…
...to the woman who, in one year from today, will become...
牙医师巴瑞•法伯太太
...Mrs. Dr. Barry Farber, D.D.S.
我想是再看一次戒指的时候了
I think it's time to see the ring again.
这真的是太棒了 好像跟男朋友在一起一辈子一样
Ugh! Isn't it exciting? I mean, it's like having a boyfriend for life! Heh!
是啊 我知道
Ahem. Yeah, I know.
怎么了
What?
我不知道…
Oh, I don't know.
只是想到…
Well, maybe it's just the idea...
要跟巴瑞共度下半辈子
...of Barry for the rest of my life.
我不知道 我觉得自己…
I don't know, I think I...
应该在那之前放纵一下
I feel like having one last fling...
让自己发泄掉所有欲望
...just to sort of get it out of my system.
- 瑞秋 别说了   - 你好坏喔
- Rachel, stop!     - You're so bad! Ha!
我是认真的 我真的觉得我得…
I'm serious. I really think I need to just have...
来点无意义的性爱
...some meaningless sex, you know?
跟下一个我看到的男人
With the next guy I see.
抱歉 我的球 好像掉了
Excuse me, I seem to have dropped my ball.
所以呢
Yeah, so?
现在我又把它捡了起来
And now I've picked it up again.
天啊 我跟她一起念过高中
My God! I went to high school with her.
瑞秋
Rachel!
嗨
Hi.
摩妮卡
Monica!
看看你 你好 你觉得美吗
Look! Hi! What do you think?
天啊
Oh, my God!
完全看不出来被泰坦尼克号撞过
You can't even see where the Titanic hit it.
他叫做巴瑞 他是个医生 谢谢
Yes, his name is Barry. He's a doctor, thank you very much.
跟你梦想的一样 恭喜了
Aw, just like you always wanted. Congratulations.
谢谢 那你呢 你有对象吗
Thank you. So how about you? Are you seeing anybody?
现在没有
Not right now.
噢 没有关系啊
Oh, well, that's okay.
我知道
I know.
我得回去跟我朋友打球了
So I think I'll get back to my friend.
当然
Oh, yeah. Sure, sure, sure.
下一次我进城的时候 一起吃午餐好吗
Can we have lunch the next time I'm in the city?
那一定会很棒
That'd be great.
- 好 再见   - 谢谢 再见
- Okay. Bye.     - Thanks. Bye.
赌十块钱 我再也不会看到她了
Ten bucks says I never see that woman again in my life.
不 亲爱的 没关系
No, honey, really. It's fine.
跟苏珊去
Just go with Susan.
真的 我认为…
Really, I think...
我觉得女生之夜是很棒的主意
I think girls' night out is a great idea.
好 再见
Okay. Okay. Bye.
- 她们要做什么   - 不知道 女生的事情
- What are they doing?     - I don't know. Something girly.
嘿 你回来早了
Hey, you're early.
你拿着灯干嘛
What are you doing with the lamp?
要拿去重新装电线
Just taking it to get rewired.
不要拿去你修音响的地方 已经修一个礼拜了
Don't take it where you took the stereo. They've had that over a week.
不 海克斯先生 没有人在这里发出噪音
No, no. Mr. Heckles, no one is making any noise up here.
你们干扰我的双簧管练习
You're disturbing my oboe practice.
- 你又不会吹双簧管   - 我可能会吹
- You don't play the oboe.     - I could play the oboe.
那我要请你小声一点
Then I'm gonna have to ask you to keep it down.
你是谁
Who are you?
- 我是艾瑞克 钱德的新室友   - 我才是钱德的新室友
- I'm Eric, Chandler's new roommate.     - I'm Chandler's new roommate.
- 我不这么认为   - 我可以是钱德的新室友
- I don't think so.     - I could be Chandler's new roommate.
- 但他在电话中说…   - 他亲自跟我说的
- But he told me over the phone...     - He told me in person.
真是奇怪
That's weird.
我要回去我的新公寓里了
I'm going to, uh, go into my new apartment now.
嗨 又见面了
Hi again.
嘿
Hey.
真的很谢谢你
Thank you so much.
不用谢我 谢那个放我鸽子的混蛋
Don't thank me. Thank the jerk that never showed up.
好 我得去工作了
Okay, I gotta get to work.
- 需要帮忙吗   - 谢了 我没问题
- You want some help?     - No, thanks. I got it.
才怪
No, I don't!
- 没事吧    - 嗯
- You okay?     - Yeah. Phew!
我太快站起来了 有点头晕
I stood up too fast. Got a little head rush.
是天气太热了
It's the heat.
又潮湿
And the humidity.
对 这是…
That's...
很糟糕的组合
...a tough combination.
你想进来喝点柠檬汁吗
Do you want to come in for some lemonade?
你绝对不会相信我有多想
Like you wouldn't believe.
很棒的地方
Wow. This is a great place.
谢谢
Thank you.
当作自己家
Just make yourself comfortable.
懂了
Gotcha.
这里其实是我奶奶的公寓
So this place is really my grandmother's.
她搬去佛罗里达时我才接手 不然我根本负担不起
I got it when she moved to Florida. Otherwise I could never afford it.
如果房东问起…
So if the landlord ever asks...
我是个害怕录放影机的 八十七岁老太太 你口渴吗
...I'm an 87-year-old woman who's afraid of her VCR. You thirsty?
超渴的
You bet I am!
好…
Okay...
你的"小弟"来了
...here's your penis!
天啊 你在干什么
Oh, my God! What the hell are you doing?
是你请我进来喝点柠檬汁的
You said, "You wanna come in for some lemonade?"
所以呢
So?
- 你只是要给我柠檬汁喝   - 对
- Ah! Were you just gonna give me lemonade?     - Yuh-huh!
穿点衣服
Cover yourself up!
对喔 抱歉
Oh, right. Sorry.
天啊 真不敢相信
God, I don't believe this!
有人问你要不要喝柠檬汁就代表想上床吗
Someone asks you in for lemonade and that means they want to have sex?
通常是的 不只是柠檬汁…
Usually, yeah. Well, not just lemonade...
柠檬红茶 有时候是果汁
...iced tea, sometimes juice.
听好 真的很对不起 我只是…
Look, sorry. I just...
我以为你喜欢我
I thought you liked me.
我真是个混蛋
I'm such a jerk.
没关系
It's okay.
这有可能发生在任何人身上
I suppose it could happen to anyone.
不是我认识的人 但是…
Not anyone I know, but...
还有 我还是看得到
By the way, I can still see it.
菲比
Pheebs?
你的床呢
Where's your bed?
不在公寓里
It's not in the apartment?
不会吧
Oh, no!
我不敢相信 这又发生了
I can't believe this is happening again.
- 什么   - 好了 不需要再用质问的语气了
- What?     - Okay, enough with the third degree!
我不住在这里了
I don't live here anymore.
- 你在说什么   - 对不起
- What are you talking about?     - I'm sorry.
我不住在这里了
I don't live here anymore.
我不知道怎么跟你说 但是其他人都知道
I didn't know how to tell you. But, you know, everybody else knows.
大家都知道
Everybody knows?
这应该是件好事的 我忘记原因了
That was supposed to be a good thing. I forget why.
摩妮卡 我有一个月的时间睡不着觉
Monica, do you know I couldn't sleep for a month...
因为沙发的抱枕上有个小黑点
...because I got a dot of ink on one of the sofa cushions?
你可以把抱枕翻面啊
You could've just turned the cushion over.
本来会的 但是另外一边有意大利面污渍
I would have, but I had a spaghetti stain on the other side.
什么
What?
我就是这个意思
This is what I'm talking about.
我需要住在一个可以弄脏的地方
I need to live in a land where people can spill!
你可以啊
Well, you can spill.
在水槽就行
In the sink.
亲爱的 这不是你的错 这是你的本性
Oh, honey. It's not your fault, you know. This is who you are.
我很爱你 我希望我们能当朋友
And I love you. And I want us to be friends.
如果我留在这里 就没办法了
And if I stay here, I don't see that happening.
- 我也爱你   - 好
- I love you too.     - Good.
怎么了
What?
怎么了 我只是难过而已
What? I'm just sad.
才不是 你想问抱枕在哪里
No, you're not. You're wondering which cushion it is.
你在看什么
So what are you watching?
"海滩游侠"
Baywatch.
在演什么
What's it about?
救生员
Lifeguards.
嗯 听起来有点蠢…
Well, it sounds kind of stup...
她是谁啊
Who's she?
妮可•艾吉特
Nicole Eggert.
我们都喜欢她
We like her.
看她们跑步的样子
Wow! Look at them run!
她们常这样
They do that a lot.
想喝点啤酒吗
Hey, you want a beer?
- 我去拿   - 不用站起来 我这里有个冷藏箱
- I'll get one.     - Don't get up. I got a cooler here.
- 哈罗   - 嘿
- Hello?     - Hey.
你有啤酒吗 我们喝完了
Do you have any beers? We're out of beers.
自己拿
Help yourself.
你没事吧
You okay?
菲比搬出去了
Phoebe moved out.
对喔
Right.
我不懂
I don't understand.
跟我住那么困难吗 这是我没有男友的原因吗
Am I so hard to live with? Is this why I don't have a boyfriend?
不…
No...
你没有男友是因为…
You don't have a boyfriend because...
我不知道为什么你没有男友
I don't know why you don't have a boyfriend.
你应该要有的
You should have a boyfriend.
我是这么认为
I think so.
过来
Come here.
听好 你是我最喜欢的人之一
Listen, you are one of my favorite people...
也是我在真实生活中认识最美丽的女生之一
...and the most beautiful woman I've ever known in real life.
嗨
Hi.
大家都去哪了
Where is everybody?
已经关门了 克里斯给我钥匙让我锁门 怎么了
Ugh, it's already closed. Chris gave me the keys to lock up. What is wrong?
我想我的婚姻…
I think my marriage...
已经结束了
...is kind of over.
不会吧 怎么了
Oh, no! Why?
因为卡萝是女同志
Because Carol's a lesbian.
而我不是女同志
And I'm not one.
很明显不是男女的搭配
And apparently it's not a mix-and-match situation.
天啊
Oh, my God!
我不敢相信
I don't believe it!
你这可怜的家伙
Oh, you poor bunny.
我是个白痴
I'm an idiot.
我早该料到的
I mean, I should have seen it.
卡萝和我出门时 她如果看到漂亮的女生…
I mean, Carol and I would be out, and she'd see some beautiful woman...
就会说 "罗斯 你快看"
...and she'd be, "Ross! Look at her!"
我心里就会想说…
And I'd think:
"天啊 我老婆太酷了"
"God, my wife is cool." Heh.
嘿 你觉得那个苏珊是她的爱人吗
Aw. Hey, do you think that Susan person is her lover?
我现在是这么想了
Well, now I do!
真抱歉
I'm sorry.
七年了
Seven years!
我们在一起七年了
I mean, we've been together seven years.
她是唯一爱过我的女人
She's the only woman who's ever loved me.
她是我唯一…
She's the only woman I've ever...
噢 罗斯
Oh, Ross.
感觉真好
Mm. This is nice.
我知道 真的很舒服吧
I know. It is, isn't it?
我是说真的 真的很舒服
No, I mean it. This feels really good.
是百分之百纯棉吗
Is it 100 percent cotton?
是啊
Yeah...
而且是折扣的时候买的
...and I got it on sale too.
我得走了
I should go.
其中一个救生员即将拆除核弹装置
One of the lifeguards was just about to dismantle a nuclear device.
如果你想要的话 待会儿可以一起喝点东西
If you want to get a drink later, we can.
听起来很棒
That sounds great.
噢 还有 应该…
Oh, and listen, it's gonna be...
我知道
I know.
谢谢
Thanks.
如果我更关心她 或更注意她
Maybe this wouldn't have happened if I'd been more nurturing...
这一切或许就不会发生了
...or I'd paid more attention...
有子宫也行
...or I had a uterus.
- 我不敢相信   - 我知道
- I can't believe it.     - I know.
你不该这样被对待 真的 罗斯
You know, you don't deserve this. You don't, Ross.
- 你真的很棒   - 谢谢
- You're so good.     - Thanks.
而且你很温柔
And you're so sweet.
- 谢谢   - 人又好
- Thanks.     - And you're kind.
谢谢
Thanks.
过来
Come here.
等等…
Wait, wait, wait.
没关系
It's okay.
等等  我的脚卡在球袋里
Wait, wait, wait! My foot is stuck in the pocket.
- 怎么了   - 我拿不出来
- What?     - I can't get it out.
女生可不想听到这个
That's not something a girl wants to hear.
别提这个
Come on, don't start.
又怎么了
What?
愚蠢的球卡在中间
Stupid balls are in the way.
嗯…
Oh, well.
那大概不会是最有建设性的解决方法
That probably wouldn't have been the most constructive solution.
你脸上有撞球粉
You have chalk on your face.
你说得没错 我不知道 为什么老是以为这是真草
Ugh. You're right. I don't know why I always thought this was real grass.
你没事吧
Honey, you okay?
我老婆是同性恋
My wife's a lesbian.
真酷
Cool!
罗斯 这是乔伊 乔伊 这是罗斯
Ross, Joey. Joey, Ross.
我不敢相信你回来了
I can't believe you came back.
什么都不要说
Don't say anything.
我不想说话 不想思考
I don't wanna speak. I don't wanna think.
我只要你抱我 亲我 和我做爱
I just want you to take me and kiss me and make love to me right here...
就是现在
...right now.
# 这是爱的季节 #
# It's the time of the season #
# 爱情的火焰高涨  #
# When love runs high #
瑞秋
Rachel!
- 怎么了   - 你错过出口了
- What?     - You missed the exit.
对不起
Oh! Sorry.
天啊 你在想什么
My God, what were you thinking about?
巴瑞
Barry.